It's why I argue and it's right at the root of
这就是我争论的原因，也是我发起
the courage to teach movement
教学勇气运动的根本所在，
that good teaching can never be reduced to technique.
即好的教学永远不能简化为技术。
Good teaching comes from
好的教学来自于
the identity and integrity of the teacher.
教师的自身认同和自身完整。
That is from the heart of the teacher,
那是来自于教师的内心，
from the selfhood of the teacher,
来自于教师的自我身份，
who's capable of standing in
他能够站在这个
this very complex field of forces and
非常复杂的力量领域中，
continuously and generously offering
在这个好客的背景下
hospitality safety and challenge within
不断地、慷慨地提供
that hospitable context.
友善、安全和挑战。
To fearful students who are trying to learn
对于那些试图学习非常可怕东西的
very fearsome things that takes a courageous person.
带有恐惧的学生，他们需要一个勇敢的老师。
It's not a mechanic we're asking for here.
我们在这里需要的不是一个机械师。
It's a person who's engaged, is involved,
我们需要的是一个能参与其中、投入其中的教师，
who's  speaking from their integrity
他们要从自身完整出发进行教学，
and not just from some textbook.
而不只是从教科书进行教学。